elecite.com 2010-11-20

# BlackBerry Themes - Elecite

Check out our collection of   
Blackberry Themes.

Beware - instant popularity   
may occur...

Get super-secret emails on   
things you are otherwise   
certain to miss out on

Privacy Policy

At Elecite, we want to be sure you are knowledgeable about and comfortable with how we handle information about you. This policy will explain what information we collect, how it is used, whether it is shared with others and how we keep our systems as secure as possible, as well as your role in protecting against loss of your privacy.

**Please read this carefully, as your continued use of the website is evidence that you have consented to these terms.**  
_____________________________________________________________________________________________

**  
What information is collected by Elecite via this website?**

•    Information about you – we actively collect personal information about you when you provide it voluntarily. This information may include your name, email address, phone number, credit card details (e.g., type, expiry date), postal address and other information as defined by applicable federal, state or local law. 

•    Information about your computer or mobile device – we may passively collect information about your computer and/or mobile device, such as your Internet domain name, IP address, device and/or phone number, the type of browser your computer is using, the date and time of your visit, and the page(s) you visited on our website or in an on-device catalogue (if applicable). This is done automatically using a variety of tools, including cookies, server log files and other forms of navigational data collection, including, without limitation, pixel tags, web beacons or clear GIFs. 

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
  
**  
What is Elecite’s reason for collecting this information?**

The personal information collected from you is used to respond to your request for Elecite products and services, for provision of such products and services, to determine your satisfaction with your purchase(s) and to customise our future interactions to meet your needs. The information about your computer and/or your mobile device is used to analyse marketing statistics, identify trends and continually improve the way in which we serve you. 

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
  
**  
What if I don’t want you to passively collect information about my computer?**

Cookies and related tools should not harm your computer or mobile device, and they do not identify you personally. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of our website and on-device clients, such as the shopping cart, will not work without cookies or similar tags.

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
  
**  
What steps does Elecite take to protect my personal information, if I choose to provide it?**

Elecite employs a range of security measures, including authentication, auditing, monitoring and industry standard encryption, which is used when you provide your credit card details. We need your help to make our security measures complete. If you feel that the security of your communications with us has been compromised, contact us immediately using the contact information provided at the end of the policy. 

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
**

Are you guaranteeing that my communications with Elecite via the website are 100% secure?

**

No. There is no method of data transmission that can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse, every time. We do not ensure or otherwise warrant the security of information that you provide. We do use the tools that are commercially available to secure our systems, monitor them and adopt new and better tools as they become available. Also, we cannot vouch for the privacy measures of other websites or wireless networks, should you visit them via a link from our website. Our provision of hyperlinks is for your convenience and does not imply that Elecite endorses or has an association with the linked sites. Please note that if you transmit your information using an on-device client, your information will be travelling over the wireless network provided by your network provider and Elecite cannot ensure the privacy of your information when it travels over such third party networks.

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
**

Will you be sharing my personal or computer information with others?

**

Your personal information may be shared with our business partners, such as software developers, network providers, device manufacturers and/or certain retailers, in order to fulfill your request for Elecite products and services. These business partners should not use this information for any purpose other than to fulfill your request, but we cannot ensure that their confidentiality policies are the same as ours. Your computer information, which does not identify you personally, will be aggregated with the information on other website users for analysis, which may be done by Elecite or by a subcontractor. Your information may also be released if disclosure is required by law, in the event of a corporate sale, merger or similar event, or our systems administrators need to access the information as part of an investigation into technical problems (e.g., spider, bot, worm), vandalism, or other misuse of the Elecite website or on-device clients.

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
**

What does Elecite do to limit access to the website by children?

**

Our website is intended for use by adults and is not structured to attract children. We do not directly seek children as users of our products and services without their parents’ knowledge and consent, nor do we indirectly appeal to them by using animated characters or similar attractions. Persons under the age of 13 should not submit their personal information, or the personal information of their family or friends, via the website or an on-device client. If you believe that your child has provided personal information via our website, please contact us and we will remove the information from our systems.

_____________________________________________________________________________________________  
**

Where do I go for additional information about privacy or to report a concern?

**

If you have any comments or questions, we want to hear from you. If you are purchasing via the Elecite, please send an email to info (at) elecite (dot) com. 

_____________________________________________________________________________________________

_Due to continuing changes in the legal, practical, and technical aspects of protecting your privacy, this policy will be updated periodically. Please check back here from time to time, especially before you provide your personal information via the website, so that you are always up to date on this important issue._
